I met a little boy in the mountains.
Who could barely speak Mandarin.
An ethnic minority boy.
He didn't seem to have much schooling, either.
How tall was he?
How tall was the little boy?
About... this tall.
So he saw you.
And then?
He lived in the woods
with his dad.
His adoptive father, that is.
The little boy was really cute.
With dark skin.
And dark eyes.
And he gave every tree
a name that only he knew.
Every tree?
Every tree had a name?
As if the trees were his friends.
You... You just mentioned his adoptive father.
Right. That call just now
was to tell me his adoptive father got arrested.
And it seems the kid's family
wants the child back.
So the two sides got into some sort of conflict.
People from Rongshan...
Why would they be arrested and brought here?
They didn't explain it clearly on the phone.
Anyway, they just want me to go over there.
Will you take Lao Kang's case?
I don't know.
They probably just see me as a familiar face,
and want me to help ask around about the situation.
Do you know if there are
any cheap and reliable budget hotels nearby?
How could a cheap one be reliable?
Why don't you choose a nicer, more comfortable one?
I'd love to.
But...
I'm in a bit of a tricky situation right now.
Why?
To stop me from moving out, my mom
cut off my financial support.
So from now on, I can only
survive on the bonuses from my cases.
But no one dares to bring me any cases now.
But I really can't
continue living like this.
Then I'll lend you money.
Really?
No, I didn't ask you out
to borrow money from you.
Have you considered that you're a girl?
Why would you look for unsafe hotels?
You're also a lawyer, you know?
I'm not some hotshot lawyer with enemies.
Listen to me.
It's because after you reported me,
you suffered a lot of negative backlash.
But I don't think you did anything wrong.
If anything, you were dragged down with me.
Look,
I appreciate the gesture.
But it's really unnecessary.
Thank you.
I can solve this myself.
Alright, it's getting late.
You should head back early.
If you accept my proposal,
we'll call it even for you reporting me.
Besides,
it's not a free loan.
You have to write an IOU.
Loans must be repaid,
and there will be interest.
Can't you let an unemployed old man
earn some extra cash?
You'll need to write an IOU.
With interest, of course.
Okay.
The people at your court gave me attitude,
but I didn't regret it.
My colleagues and boss talked behind my back,
but I still didn't regret it.
Even when that male caregiver's girlfriend
terminated her contract with me,
I didn't regret it at all.
But for a moment just now,
I really kind of regretted reporting you.
Why? What do you mean?
I only mentioned
the name Lao Kang once on the phone.
I can't believe you remembered.
What do you think
someone with Alzheimer's is like?
Like a crashed computer?
Just a black screen with nothing on it?
Let me tell you,
if you need a place to stay,
you'd better go to 128 Zhongshan Road.
To that hotel.
Because there's a police station next door.
If anything happens,
the police will be there in two minutes.
It's a bit safer.
Will you remember?
Write it down if you can't.
In case you forget.
You decide how much to borrow.
I just transferred the money to you.
See if it's enough.
Is it okay? Is it enough?
Thank you.
Thank me?
There will be interest.
Thank you for giving me a chance
to get even with you.
First time borrowing money in my life.
What a coincidence.
It's my first time lending money to someone, too.
He gave every tree
a name only he knew,
as if that tree were his friend.
Hello?
Zhao Yijie, I want to ask you...
You said
you had already found a lawyer for Lao Kang.
But today, a friend of mine
also got a call about Lao Kang's case.
What does this mean?
This is none of your business.
It just hasn't been driven in a while.
Change the tires and the battery,
then change the oil,
and it should be fine.
Lao Kong, I'm here on serious business.
I need you to help me find someone's address.
That's easy.
A few phone calls and I'll have it.
Whose?
The founder of Rujie Law Firm, Zhao Yijie.
Name your price.
I know the rules.
About what you just said,
I couldn't do it for any amount of money.
Why not?
Can't you just help me this once?
I am helping you right now.
Just stay out of this mess, okay?
That place, Rujie...
I can't tell you too much about it.
Anyway, just trust me.
Stop asking around.
Lao Kong, you need to explain it to me today.
Why?
You went to Rujie to look for Zhao Yijie.
That's no secret.
Word has already spread.
Those law firms that wanted to hire you
have all given up.
Who in the entire legal circle isn't avoiding him?
Whenever Zhao Yijie has his eye on someone or a case,
no one dares to fight him for it.
That's my business.
If I tell you where he lives,
I have a wife and kids to think about.
Lao Kong, I'm just curious.
You're not afraid to cause trouble at the court,
but you're afraid of him?
What is he? The mafia?
The mafia is nothing compared to him.
Let me tell you.
Without Zhao Yijie,
half of Jiangliu City would stop running.
I've told you too much.
I can't say anymore.
Alright then.
I won't bother you anymore.
Thanks. I'll find someone else.
No.
You can't ask anyone else.
Whoever you ask,
word will get to Zhao Yijie's ears.
I get it.
I'm unemployed now.
People sure turn their backs fast, huh?
That's uncalled for.
You're so stubborn.
I give up.
Well, that receptionist at Rujie...
She looks unremarkable,
but she actually helped Zhao Yijie build his business from scratch.
If you want to know his address,
follow that receptionist for a few days.
You should get some results.
Are you saying they...
Uh, I'll call you when the car is fixed.
I'll just drop it off at your house.
Go ahead and get busy.
I know, Mr. Ye.
Winning or losing a lawsuit
is something no one can guarantee.
If Lao Kang really broke the law,
then even the best lawyer
couldn't argue that black is white for him.
You mean the family that adopted Yang A'wu
got a lawyer for Lao Kang?
I'll call you back later.
Bye.
What did you want to see me about?
Good news.
Rujie gave me a case.
An armed robbery from four years ago.
A criminal case?
Yeah.
And the client
is a distant relative of our boss.
So if we handle this case well,
getting you into Rujie
shouldn't be a problem.
I'm doing perfectly fine at Changyu.
Why would I go to Rujie?
Is this all you wanted?
Out of all the lawyers I know,
you're the best at criminal cases.
So I was thinking,
maybe we could
team up like the old days?
A 60-40 split in your favor.
Let me think about it.
What is there to hesitate about?
This is a great stepping stone for you, Ding Ning.
For a law firm like Rujie,
its industry reputation and status
go without saying.
I know you don't care about that anyway.
The point is, Rujie has top-tier clients.
You'll never have to worry about winning a case
only for the client to refuse to pay.
Plus, at Rujie,
you only need to focus on one or two cases a year
and that's enough to support yourself.
It's nothing like our mentor's low-margin, high-volume approach.
I have to head out now.
Give me an answer tomorrow.
Okay?
I'm off.
Free to meet up in a bit?
The guy you mentioned before...
The lunatic threatening to get back at me?
Did you find out who he is?
I did.
Just some bored guy.
He's all talk.
Nothing to worry about.
Crisis averted.
What about you?
Weren't you going to Rongshan?
Not anymore.
We couldn't agree on the price.
You know, as lawyers...
isn't it normal for us to charge?
Of course.
Why is it that whenever I bring up money,
it feels like I'm in the wrong?
Having some sweet soup?
Where did you buy it?
People line up for it every day.
It's right by that mall over there.
I just joined the line.
I waited in line all afternoon today.
Try it and see if it's good.
Give it here.
When I used to eat this stuff,
it was never this complicated.
I'm really not used to it.
Since you're not taking that case anymore,
and with Lao Kang locked up,
what about the kid, Yang A'wu?
How is he doing now?
Have you contacted him?
No.
But I've been thinking about him a lot lately.
Every time I see a tree,
I think of that little guy.
Say, if he came to the city,
would he get used to it?
Seeing the trees here,
would he adapt?
He's so young.
I don't know.
But the trees in the city
are really different from the ones in the mountains.
You see, mountain trees have their own personalities.
And their own names.
But the trees in the city
are all trimmed so neatly.
A soul as wild,
as free,
and as full of life as Yang A'wu...
He was born for that mountain forest.
You know what?
He even showed me
the graves they dug under the trees.
What graves?
It means while they're still alive,
they already dig a hole for themselves
to mark where they'll be buried after they die.
That's pretty interesting.
It means he wants to
leave his final nutrients
to the tree he loves the most.
Just like city folks
leaving their inheritance to the ones they love.
Then why don't you go see him,
or contact him?
I heard he's about to be
taken to his adoptive parents' house.
Do you have his adoptive parents' contact info?
Why would I have their contact info?
Fair enough.
But his adoptive parents must be good people, right?
Look at Lao Kang.
He tried so hard to stop them from taking the kid back before,
but when Lao Kang got into trouble,
they were still willing to find someone to help him.
I hope so.
I'd really love to meet him.
Why are you so interested
in this little kid?
Because my son,
when he was his age,
was the closest to me.
Kids around this age
are like alarms.
Whenever they're unhappy, they yell.
Like, they really scream.
Just...
about so many things.
Do you think it's genetic?
Inherited from whom?
I was never like that.
I kept everything bottled up inside.
This sweet soup is really good!
Yeah?
No wonder the line was so long.
Waiting in line is pretty interesting.
You never know if you'll
actually get your turn, you know?
You just keep waiting.
You worry that when it's finally your turn,
it might be sold out. What then?
You line up again tomorrow.
Who knows if we even have a tomorrow?
Why so pessimistic?
No, what if tomorrow I forget
the address of the sweet soup shop?
What then?
You know I have Alzheimer's,
right?
Then I'll be the one waiting in line to buy it for you.
The kid ran away!
He might be over there.
Let's go check.
Hello, Mr. Yu.
Hello, Ding Ning.
What are you doing? I told you there's no rush.
Why did you transfer the money to me so fast?
I'm definitely not going to Rongshan.
So...
Hang on a second.
Hello?
Is this Lawyer Ding Ning?
Speaking.
Hello, this is the Nanfeng Road Police Station.
Could you come to Limin Square on Nanfeng Road?
Okay, I'll head over right now.
Bye.
Mr. Yu, something urgent came up.
I have to go to Nanfeng Road right now.
Nanfeng Road?
What for?
Whose kid is this?
Hurry up and come down. It's dangerous up there.
Look.
There are too many people here at the scene right now.
We need to ensure safety.
And one more thing.
We need to notify the fire department.
Hello, I'm Ding Ning.
Did you call me?
You're Ding Ning, right?
I'm the one who called you.
Come here for a second.
Do you know this kid?
Yang A'wu?
What are you doing here?
I know him. I know this boy.
He hasn't said a word.
And we found you...
...from a business card that fell out of his pocket.
This kid usually lives in the mountains.
I guess he just arrived in the city.
He probably panicked and got lost.
And then he climbed up there.
I'll call him down.
Okay.
A'wu!
Ding Ning, Ding Ning.
Come on down.
Slowly, kid.
We'll catch you.
Come on, get down.
Careful, careful.
Watch your step.
Hold on tight.
Be careful.
Slowly, slowly.
Easy now.
Come here, I'll catch you.
Careful.
Watch your step. No rush.
It's fine, he can do it.
Come on, get down.
A'wu.
A'wu, how did you get here?
Who brought you here?
This kid climbs trees whenever he gets scared.
That's quite unusual.
What's his name?
Yang A'wu.
Yang as in poplar tree.
And A'wu as in the number five.
Yang A'wu.
A'wu.
Go to the...
Come here, it's okay.
...missing persons database and look up this name.
I'm right here.
How many days have you been here?
Your hair is such a mess.
Alright, everything's fine now.
Break it up. Time to go home.
How did you get here?
Who brought you here?
Yang A'wu
Mr. Yu, why are you here?
Sir, you are...?
We know each other.
This is...
Please check Yang A'wu's registry info.
You know him?
He's about 1.2 meters tall.
I know his adoptive father.
You know his adoptive father?
Yes.
What's his adoptive father's name?
Just a second.
Zhao Yijie.
Transfer to Zhao Yijie.
Please put me through to Zhao Yijie.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Hello, Mr. Zhao.
I'm an officer from the Nanfeng Road Police Station.
The child has been found.
Where are you?
I'm sorry.
I'm out of town right now.
Is your dad's name Zhao Yijie?
Then what about the child?
Can I speak with him?
What's the situation?
Hello? Zhao Yijie.
Yu Songfan.
Why are you there?
I've already found the child for you.
I'll take care of him for you tonight.
Let him stay at my place.
Don't even think about it.
I'll have the nanny pick him up right now.
Didn't the nanny already lose him?
Do you want to lose him again?
Listen to me.
He's staying at my place tonight.
Do you understand?
That's settled then. You're welcome.
Then explain it to the police.
Hello, Mr. Zhao.
Please leave the child with my friend for now.
Okay.
You're lucky to have a good friend.
All right, we'll leave the child with you.
Thank you. Sorry for the trouble.
No problem.
Let's go home.
Come on in. No need to take off your shoes.
Okay, okay. Let's go in.
Have a seat inside.
Do you want some milk?
How about some milk?
Do you want some?
So you're saying
Yang A'wu's adoptive father is Zhao Yijie?
It's because he used to
frequently donate to schools in Rongshan.
That's how he met A'wu
and adopted him.
Yeah.
He showed me a photo of the three of them,
so I know what he looks like.
But I didn't know his name.
That's really unexpected.
Later, you kept mentioning Yang A'wu,
turns out it's the same person.
What a coincidence.
A'wu, A'wu!
Can you get down first?
I can't breathe like this, A'wu!
A'wu!
The alarm. I see what you mean.
What should we do?
A'wu.
A'wu, can you sit down for a bit?
A'wu!
How about some milk? Milk.
A'wu, get down and sit for a moment.
Ask him to drink the milk.
Look, look at this grandpa.
Look at this grandpa.
He's just like me.
He's also your...
Your Ga'ao, Ma Wei,
and Nezha.
It's okay, don't be afraid.
He's our friend.
Don't be afraid.
Look.
What did you just say?
Is that their hometown dialect?
Come on.
Do you want the milk?
It's delicious. Come here.
No.
What does that mean?
I told you before.
They're names he gave to trees.
A'wu, did you just fart?
It stinks.
Seriously.
Take your time.
Drink up. Slowly now.
That law firm Zhao Yijie started,
is it called Rujie?
What's wrong?
Where's your bathroom?
First door on the right.
I need to use it.
Sit here for a bit.
Hello, Zhou Hao.
The case you asked me to join,
is the client a forest ranger from Rongshan?
How did you know?
Forty-sixty split.
Of course.
Then I'll send you the files right away.
Okay.
He fell asleep.
He must have been through a lot lately.
Didn't get much sleep.
Let's have something to eat.
What would you like?
Any dietary restrictions?
No need to bother.
I should probably head back.
Ding Ning.
I actually have a favor to ask.
Could you stay here tonight?
Because I'm worried that when the little guy wakes up...
...his alarm will go off again.
And I won't be able to handle him.
What if he runs off again?
It'd be really hard to explain to his parents.
Just for one night.
Consider it doing me a favor, alright?
I mean it.
Stay at your place?
I have a spare room.
No, that wouldn't be appropriate.
How about this?
If he wakes up and makes a fuss again...
...just give me a call.
As long as I'm not busy...
...I'll come right over to help look after him, okay?
Call me, okay?
Alright, sorry about this.
I'm leaving now.
A'wu.
I have to go back.
Ding Ning is leaving. Come here.
See?
A'wu, I have to go back.
I don't live here.
You stay here with Grandpa, okay?
Hear me? Come here.
How about you stay for dinner?
What do you want to eat?
I don't have any dietary restrictions.
I'll go start cooking.
No, I...
It's okay.
A'wu.
Can you get down for a second?
A'wu, okay.
I... I came back, didn't I?
How about tomato and tomato stir-fry?
I mean eggs.
Alright.
I'm heading to Rongshan again in a few days anyway.
Didn't you turn down Lao Kang's case?
Why are you going to Rongshan?
I didn't.
Right now, I'm
the assistant lawyer for Lao Kang's case.
They said this case involves a jurisdictional challenge,
so it's highly likely
it'll be sent back to the county court for trial.
A'wu. A'wu.
Jurisdictional challenge.
A'wu, Grandpa made you something delicious.
Do you like eggs?
Or do you prefer meat?
Look, see, Grandpa is cooking.
Time to eat!
Are you getting hungry?
What's your favorite food?
Do you like tomatoes stir-fried with tomatoes?
My favorite thing to eat
is you!
Are you ticklish?
So ticklish!
In Lao Kang's case,
Zhou Hao raised a jurisdictional challenge.
Mr. Zhao.
What's going on with the jurisdictional challenge?
I was just making a presentation to report to you.
Should I just give you a verbal update now?
Go ahead.
I think this case of ours is very strange.
It's moving incredibly fast.
I haven't even had time to meet with Lao Kang,
and the investigation phase is already over.
It's moving to the procuratorate's review for prosecution.
So?
Just hear me out.
For Lao Kang's case,
I have my own strategy.
There's a young judge at Fulin District Court
who just transferred from Civil to Criminal.
He told me that...
Listen to me carefully.
Stop messing with the jurisdictional challenge.
The trial stays in the local court.
Understood.
I... I was just afraid there might be flaws in our case,
so I thought...
All right, that's enough.
Thanks for your hard work.
Just doing my job.
Hey, Dad.
It's pretty good.
Going smoothly.
Rujie is better than I expected.
I've taken on quite a few cases.
Don't look down on me.
I'm telling you,
in another couple of years,
it'll be my turn to teach you about the law.
You hear me?
Make sure you take your medicine on time.
Morning.
Did you sleep okay last night?
Not bad.
I'm sorry to trouble you.
Um,
when is lawyer Zhao Yijie coming to pick him up?
I called him last night.
He said he had to go on a business trip.
I'm so annoyed.
He said he won't be back for a while.
I really...
I really don't know what to do now.
I just feel that
my staying here like this isn't a solution.
And I haven't checked out of the hotel yet.
I know.
I just feel bad about it.
I really don't know what to say.
Really, sorry to bother you.
A'wu.
Here, here, here.
Why are you hiding under the table to eat?
Come on out.
It's too dusty down here, okay?
Come out and eat, alright?
Come on out.
Come on, come out.
Eat.
It's dusty down here.
What if you get sick?
Come out, be a good boy.
Oh, A'wu...
A'wu, do you want to eat down here?
Okay.
A'wu.
Come on, we'll eat down here.
I'll eat down here with you, okay?
Ding Ning, you shouldn't do that.
There are rules for eating.
You should eat at the table.
Just take it slow.
You have to give him time to adapt.
Alright then. Okay, okay.
You're giving this to me?
Okay, okay, okay.
We'll stay right here together.
And eat down here, okay?
It's so tasty!
We'll all eat down here.
I'll eat down here too, alright?
Let's all eat down here together, okay?
It's very tasty.
It's like being under a big tree, isn't it?
Is it good?
It's good, right?
Grandpa made all of this.
Yeah.
From now on, Grandpa will cook good food for you.
Okay?
Is it tasty?
Is Grandpa's cooking good?
Tasty, tasty.
A'wu says it's tasty.
Tasty.
That's right.
Great job.
So tasty.
Eat some more.
Grandpa.
I'm Grandpa.
Grandpa. Grandpa.
A'wu just called me Grandpa.
Say it again. Grandpa.
Eat up.
Say it one more time, okay?
Grandpa.
He learns so fast.
He learns very fast.
A'wu, I have to go to work today.
You stay home and play with Grandpa, okay?
I'll be back soon.
I'll come back right after work, okay?
Morning, Mr. Yu.
Hello.
Alright.
Be good.
Stay with Grandpa.
I'm heading out.
Do you have the transcript?
The transcript?
Pulled an all-nighter.
Notice any changes?
You look haggard.
Dark circles, crow's feet.
And a bit of stubble.
Do I look more mature?
Since when is being clean-cut a burden?
What?
Dark circles and crow's feet...
Can they help you win cases?
Of course.
They make my clients trust me more.
And I can take this...
Let me remind you.
If we go back now,
we can freshen up and still get two hours of sleep
before seeing Lao Kang.
You don't need a ride?
I'll take a cab.
Morning.
Judge Yu, long time no see.
Wontons, please.
Coming right up!
Haven't had your wontons in a while.
Mr. Yu.
It's me, Sun from the Civil Division.
Hello, hello, Sun.
Why did you ignore me just now?
I didn't, it's just...
because of how I've been lately,
I didn't dare to hang around you guys.
I didn't want to bring you young folks down.
Don't say that, Mr. Yu.
After what happened to you,
I really wanted to visit you at home.
But you know,
we rarely get to interact privately.
I couldn't find your place and was worried.
What's the matter, Sun?
How have you been lately?
I transferred to the Criminal Division.
That's great!
You've always wanted to move from Civil to Criminal.
Your wish finally came true. Congratulations!
Not really, Mr. Yu.
After I transferred there,
I finally remembered what you told me before.
"It's the same everywhere."
I used to hate the busywork in Civil.
And now look at me.
I work overtime every day in Criminal.
It's so annoying.
You'll get used to it eventually.
Mr. Yu.
Glad I ran into you today.
Could you give me some pointers?
If I want my skills in the criminal division
to improve quickly in all aspects,
what exactly should I focus on?
Sun, I really shouldn't spout nonsense.
How could it be nonsense?
You're a leading expert, Mr. Yu.
Is it fraud cases?
What I mean is,
I need to have my own area of expertise
to avoid low-end competition.
Something with good prospects.
To be honest, Sun, if you really want my advice,
it's best not to be too ambitious too soon.
If you're thinking like this,
others are thinking the same way.
Everyone wants to stand out.
Everyone wants to take shortcuts.
So in the court,
people who can do solid, steady work
are extremely rare.
Actually,
the easiest way to stand out in Criminal...
W-What is it?
is being a steady judge.
You're new here,
so it's best not to be overly ambitious
and rush to take on major cases.
You need to know how to pick case types.
Some minor cases within major anti-gang operations,
the most inconspicuous ones,
for example, illegal possession
or picking quarrels and provoking trouble.
Right.
Cases like those.
Because for these minor cases,
you can refer to
how other judges and courts rule.
You should also frequently sit down with seniors
to hold meetings and study them together.
Discussing things like this
is also an opportunity to be noticed.
You really are something, Mr. Yu.
For cases involving jurisdictional challenges,
you should dismiss them when appropriate.
Don't push cases away,
because it looks bad if word gets out.
People won't say
that the court has a backlog of cases
causing an unreasonable workload.
They won't say the judges are exhausted.
They'll just say there's a problem with the judge,
blindly pursuing a high clearance rate
and making the numbers look good.
They'll only think
that these young judges
aren't proactive in their work.
Older judges, on the other hand,
aren't afraid of being talked about like that
because they have experience and confidence.
But you young people
have to consider this, right?
Right, they are seniors after all.
Right?
You really are something, Mr. Yu.
You've thought it through so thoroughly.
Sun, look at the time.
Don't be late.
You're right, Mr. Yu.
Then some other time,
I'll definitely pay you a visit, Mr. Yu.
Have a good day at work.
Enjoy your meal, Mr. Yu.